http://www.debspecs.com/privacy-debspecs/

Menu
Whats NewMen's ReadersWomen's Reading GlassesFun FashionsMy Favorite Pair(tort.-blk)Wide HeadsMetal Frame GlassesSmall FacesColor Fashion ReadersFunky Reading GlassesVintage Inspired ReadersPlastic Top-Metal BottomAnimal PrintsTransparent FramesHand PaintedTwo-Tone GlassesSALE-Great Buys Check out our clearance and every day low price sale items. Bang for your BuckWarehouse SpecialsBest Buys discount reading glassesClearance Reading Glasses & AccessoriesDaily Deals Check out our clearance and every day low price sale items.Reading SunglassesBifocal Reading SunglassesAll Reading SunglassesOverRX or SideKick Sun Clip onsLight SensitiveNo Line Progressive Multifocal and Hidden Sun BifocalsDimmer LensesClear Bi-FocalHidden Bifocals with clear lensDual Strength BifocalsAccessoriesEyeglass AccessoriesEyeglass CasesHard CasesBelt CasesSoft Eyeglass CasesLeather CasesDesk or table eyeglass holdersMultiple Eyeglass Cases for 2 Eyeglass Chains - JewelryHang-UpsLens Cleaning ClothsGreat Gift IdeasCompact N LightweightUltra Light n RimlessFolding GlassesSlim Line Readers in TubesLow Vision AidsAll Low Vision AidsLow Vision GlassesClip On - Flip Up Reading GlassesLoupesPage MagnifiersHeadband Visor MagnifiersMagnifiersLight Up MagnifiersNecklace MagnifiersComputer GlassesClearBlue No-Tint Computer GlassesMelanin Lens Computer GlassesTwo-Strength Bifocal Computer GlassesMulti Focal No-Line Reading GlassesOther Computer Glasses and clip-onsClicFrames and OpticalNeck Hang AroundsShippingUS & Canada ShippingInternational ShippingReturnsSparkly ReadersContact UsShop By ShapeAviator Reading GlassesCat EyeRound and Oval Reading GlassesShop By Strength
+.75
+1.00
+1.25
+1.50
+1.75
+2.00
+2.25
+2.50
Privacy Policy
Europe has a new GDPR Privacy Protection Act which DebSpecs strives to comply with. Right now we are re configuring our email specials so that they do not get sent to any customers in the EU. All emails will be purely transaction related. All sensitive payment information is immediately encrypted and no sensitive data is stored. Addresses, names and contact info are kept on our website solely for the purpose of assisting you should any customer service issue arise, as well as making re-ordering easier should you choose to create an online account. Address and contact data is never shared, sold or rented. We are further in the process of eliminating any ads created by visiting our site, which appear as reminders on various other sites to revisit our website. We have been selling online since 1996 and will continue to do business under the new European Union guidelines.
Our privacy policy is simple: We value your privacy.
We do not share, sell, rent our lease any of your personal information including name, phone, address, email, with anyone. This is true of any information you give us, by any means, including ordering from or contacting Debby Burk Optical.  We use the information you provide to send your requested order. If there is a question or issue about fulfilling the order or processing the transaction, we use your phone number and/or email to contact you. You will receive an email alerting you that your package has shipped. 10 days after your order, we will send an email to make sure you received it, and at that point you will have the opportunity to provide further feedback.
We will never call you or email you to try to solicit a sale. We will send you an introductory offer via email sometime within 1 month after your first order, at which point you can easily unsubscribe. You can contact help@debspecs.com to unsubscribe at any time.
We use a secure processing server when collection credit card information, which is certified PCI compliant. Hosting and/or development is provided by a PCI compliant Magento host. Questions about security or abuse should be directed to Web 2 Market, Inc.
We use picture advertising on other websites and search engines to display DebSpecs ads. The companies that disply these ads remember that your device had browsed on DebSpecs.com. They know devices by anonymous numbers, but do not have any access to any of your personal information. No name, no phone, no geographical location, etc. It works like this: As you browse DebSpecs website, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partners then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with DebSpecs.com. The techniques our partners employ DO NOT collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address, or telephone number.
You can visit this page to opt out of targeted advertising.
If you receive an email from us it is because 1) a direct request was made from your email address or 2)we have a working relationship with you,  namely, you are an established customer. You can opt out of informational emails at any time. Either click the "remove" link at the bottom of the email or write "remove" to Help@DebSpecs.com
or call 1-800-789-6322
Copyright © 2020 Debby Burk Optical. All Rights Reserved.
